
var English = [
  {
    "question"  : " 1. Our government is making determined efforts to eradicate illiteracy.",
     "choice"   : ["compulsory","ineffective", "innocent", "unreliable"],                  
     "correct"  : 2
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "2. Makerere University has a large intake of students each year",
     "choice"   : ["rejection", "product",  "output",  "turn-out"],                       
     "correct"  : 1
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "3. Florence flogged the girl reluctantly.",
     "choice "  : ["eagerly", "calmly", "furiously", "laboriously"],                         
     "correct"  : 2
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "4. Sola’s car is badly damaged; he has to look for an expert mechanic to fix it.",
     "choice"   : ["uneducated", "amateurish", "awkward",  "unscientific"],                         
     "correct"  : 2
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "5. Coastal plains are often very densely populated.",
     "choice"   : ["weakly", "badly", "rarely", "sparsely"],                        
     "correct"  : 4
  },
  {
    "question"  : "6. Wilfredwas a mindless criminal.",
     "choice"   :  ["strong", "mindful", "feeling",  "memorable"],                      
     "correct"  : 3
  },
  {
    "question"  : "7. The judge blamed the plaintiff for misleading the court.",
     "choice"   : ["defendant",  "complainant",  "accused",  "prosecution"],                        
     "correct"  : 1
  },
  {
    "question"  : "8. The thieves vandalized the vault’s lock.",
     "choice"   : ["repaired",  "arranged", "serviced",  "actuated"],                        
     "correct"  : 1
  },
  {
    "question"  : "9. The demonstrators have refused to call off their action.",
     "choice"   : ["consolidate", "start", "resume", "end"],                     
     "correct"  : 3
  },
  {
    "question"  : "10. The angry waves swallowed the boat.",
     "choice"   : ["gentle", "unruffled",  "cool",  "serene"],   
     "correct"  : 4
  }
  
]